[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What British film director, born in Shanghai, China, directed three, including the first in the series of James Bond movies - Dr. No (1962), From Russia with Love (1963), and Thunderball (1965)?", "correct_answer": "Terence Young", "incorrect_answers": ["Guy Hamilton", "John Glen", "Lewis Gilbert"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The 1979 movie The Amityville Horror was filmed in Amityville New York.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these could be an answer to a math problem involving volume?", "correct_answer": "8 cubic inches", "incorrect_answers": ["The are all the same", "8 inches", "8 square inches"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Listen to the audio and name the performer.", "correct_answer": "David Bowie", "incorrect_answers": ["Phil Collins", "John Lennon", "Freddie Mercury"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which city and state was the first motion picture created?", "correct_answer": "West Orange, NJ", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicago, IL", "Hollywood, CA", "Alexandria, VA"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tradition of proposing with a diamond engagement ring can be dated back to 1477 when the Archduke Maximilian of Hamburg gave one to Mary of Burgundy.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a horror movie?", "correct_answer": "Gods and Monsters", "incorrect_answers": ["Urban Legends", "Candyman", "Hostel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Pink is a line of lingerie by Victorias Secret.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The dinosaur in the movie Meet the Robinsons said this famous line: I have little head and big arms.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Larger than Pluto and Mercury, this natural satellite is the largest moon of the entire solar system.", "correct_answer": "Ganymede", "incorrect_answers": ["Titan", "Callisto", "Europa"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This unit of length, used mostly for maritime and aviation purposes, measures exactly 1.852 km (1.150779 miles).", "correct_answer": "Nautical mile", "incorrect_answers": ["Furlong", "Parsec", "Angstrom"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The young of which of these animals is not called a joey?", "correct_answer": "dog", "incorrect_answers": ["opossum", "wombat", "kangaroo"]}]